

LENNARD MARCUS SUMADRAJI

Plant Process Trainer / Assessor/ Verifier

PROFILE

I am an experienced oil and gas process Training professional with 35 years of experience within the oil industry. I have training experience with classroom; online and OJT. I am a City and Guilds and Chieti Certified Facilitator and Assessor. I'm a certified Opito Verifier. I have trained in the middle East and South Africa

CONTACT

PHONE: +27644558618

LinkedIn profile https://www.linkedin.com/in/marcussumadraji-7b962ba0

EMAIL: Lmsumadraji@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Institute of People Management

03/2000 - 03/2003

This is a NQF level 6 diploma with specialization in Training management, project management and Human Resource Management.

Sastri college

02/1985 – 12/1986 N3 and N4 electrical certificate.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Aurik Enterprise Development – Operations Facilitator

07/10/2023 - Present

Freelance remote facilitator for small to medium business development. Help business owners develop operations capability

SNV Lavalin - Lead Trainer

08/2019-10/2022

Lead Classroom and OJT training. Started up and managed the KIPIC Training Academy. Lead with the development of training materials. Developed OJT task book.

PPM Sinter - Job Task Developer

11/2017 - 02/2019

Developed progression routes for operators. Lead a team of engineers to develop a question bank for online assessment for all job levels

Aramco / Niti - Technical Skills Trainer

06/2014 - 08/2017

Did classroom and OJT training; proctored tests and submitted trainee progress reports.

Sapref – Field operator / DCS technician / Team Leader / Zone Trainer 06/1988 - 05/2014

Various roles at Sapref (Shell & BP). Did on line training for 6 years and contractor and refresher HSE training for 3 years. Developed OJT Task books for the Platformer; HDS and Crude Distiller.

SKILLS

- Training Facilitation / Assessment and verification
- Devoloping Training programmes
- Managing training process
- Managing people
- Doing gap analysis
- Doing training need analysis
- Report writing
- Trainer Assessment

TRAINING KNOWLEDGE AND EXPERIENCE

<u>Hse</u>

CSE / Hotwork / Working at elevations / HIRA / Permit issuer and receiver / PPE / Excavation risks.

Process Plants

Platformer / HDS / Alkylation / Amine Treaters / SWS / Crude Distiller / HVU / Tankage

<u>Utilities</u>
Cooling water / fuel gas / steam / firewater